what's going on ladies and gentlemen and
as you can see here we have a ape or
this is amc entertainment holdings
overall this is the preferred equity
units okay each is called you can just
read it like right here but then i'm
going to start from the
you don't even have a daily uh
only have one bill you cannot cause this
thing open today
now
if i really have to do a quick top-down
analysis on this thing you will be on
the one minute or so
like the five or so minutes
and then yeah i can start from here so
overall we broke the structure where we
open right here there
we came back from
these highs
and now it does seem like he may just
continue to leave it lower here if
that's the case or you can just deliver
a little bit higher than deliver low in
my personal opinion but again this is
only even lost just a five minute chart
so stay tuned i'm gonna be keeping you
updated more and have a wonderful day
see you
make sure just keep in mind this is not
financial guys